[{"question":"<p>but, yet, except</p><p>I can't go to the movies, but I want to watch the movie.</p>","answer":"pero<p>No puedo ir al cine, pero quiero ver la película.</p>","categories":["conjunction"]},{"question":"<p>to see</p><p>I see the television every day.</p>","answer":"<p>ver</p><p>yo veo, tú ves, él/ella ve, nosotros/as vemos, vosotros/as veis, ellos/as ven</p><p>Yo veo la televisión todos los días.</p>","categories":["verb"]},{"question":"<p>he, [ellos] them (m)</p><p>He is a good friend.</p>","answer":"él<p>Él es un buen amigo.</p>","categories":["pronoun"]},{"question":"<p>I (subj)</p><p>I am a student.</p>","answer":"yo<p>Yo soy un estudiante.</p>","categories":["pronoun"]},{"question":"<p>large, great, big</p><p>The car is big.</p>","answer":"grande<p>El coche es grande.</p>","categories":["adjective"]},{"question":"<p>she, [ellas] them (f)</p><p>She is very intelligent.</p>","answer":"ella<p>Ella es muy inteligente.</p>","categories":["pronoun"]},{"question":"<p>good</p><p>It is good for health.</p>","answer":"bueno<p>Es bueno para la salud.</p>","categories":["adjective"]},{"question":"<p>child, little boy</p><p>The children play in the park.</p>","answer":"<p>el  niño, pl. niños</p><p>Los niños juegan en el parque.</p>","categories":["noun"]},{"question":"<p>we (subj)</p><p>We talk a lot.</p>","answer":"nosotros<p>Nosotros hablamos mucho.</p>","categories":["pronoun"]},{"question":"<p>white</p><p>The dress is white.</p>","answer":"blanco<p>El vestido es blanco.</p>","categories":["adjective"]},{"question":"<p>book</p><p>The book is on the table.</p>","answer":"<p>el  libro, pl. libros</p><p>El libro está en la mesa.</p>","categories":["noun"]},{"question":"<p>it (subj-n)</p><p>It is important.</p>","answer":"ello<p>Ello es importante.</p>","categories":["pronoun"]},{"question":"<p>red</p><p>The car is red.</p>","answer":"rojo<p>El coche es rojo.</p>","categories":["adjective"]},{"question":"<p>you (subj-sg/+fam)</p><p>You are my best friend.</p>","answer":"tú<p>Tú eres mi mejor amigo.</p>","categories":["pronoun"]},{"question":"<p>they</p><p>They eat rice.</p>","answer":"ellos, ellas<p>Ellos comen arroz.</p>","categories":["pronoun"]},{"question":"<p>you (pl.)</p><p>You (all) have a car.</p>","answer":"vosotros<p>Vosotros teneis un coche.</p>","categories":["pronoun"]}]